firstclasswatches.com 2014-08-04

# Cookie Policy Information for First Class Watches

This website requires cookies to work, you may be redirected to this page if you're web browser does not accept cookies and you try to use a function which requires them. If you would like guidance on how to enabled cookies consult your browser settings or help files or to place an order by telephone call 01926 298499.

By using this website, you agree to allow us to set cookies on your computer to allow our website to perform and function as intended. We also use cookies to record usage, personalise advertising and generate statistics to allow us to provide a better service. If you do not agree to this, you should delete our cookies and alter your browser settings to prevent cookies being set.

We make use of cookies to enable our systems to recognise your browser and provide our services to yourself. A cookie is a small piece of text that we save onto your computer and is sent back to us every time you visit our website until the cookie expires. The majority of cookies that we use are essential to providing our services to you or for generating feedback on how they are used. For example, recently viewed products and saving items into your shopping basket require cookies to be accepted.

For a detailed list of the cookies we use on our website, please click on the tabs above.

First party cookies include cookies that are set directly by our website, they are sent back to us every time you request another web page from our site. These are used to personalise pages and strengthen the security of the connection between us and your web browser.

Cookie Names| Expiry| Category| Description  
---|---|---|---  
osCsid| 14 days| General| Powers website shopping basket, checkout, recently viewed products, account functions and personalised website functions  
cookie_test| 30 days| General| Used to check whether your web browser accept cookies or not  
__utma, __utmb, __utmz, __utmv, __utmx| 30 minutes to 2 years| Analytics & Research| Google Analytics software cookies. These cookies allow us to measure statistics of the way you and others use our site. For example, the number of visitors or pages viewed. For information on how Google uses this information please visit [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics).   
webgains_affiliate| 90 days| Advertising| Used to track whether or not you have visited from an affiliated partner website  
__ar_v4| 6 years+| Advertising| A Google/YouTube/Display Network cookie which tracks clicks and views on websites across the Google properties and advertising network  
  
These cookies are saved on your computer by third party websites. We may use plugins, images, scripts or other resources on our pages provided by third parties. When these resources are requested from the third party they may set cookies on your computer. These are sent back to the provider each time you load that resource, this allows them to collect data across different websites that use their plugins and resources. To find out what data third parties collect, and how it is used you are advised to consult their respective privacy policies. As the data collected and cookies these services use are subject to change, we do not list an exhaustive list of cookies for these providers.

Service Provider| Service| Description  
---|---|---  
[YouTube](http://www.youtube.com/)| Embedded Videos| When a video is displayed on our site, YouTube records this and other performance information such as view count.  
[GDM Digital](http://www.gdmdigital.com/)| Personalised Advertising| We use GDM Digital to display personalised advertising on other websites. Please see their policy on data collection.  
[Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/)| Sharing Plugin| We use a Facebook plugin to display the Facebook Like button on our pages. This sets cookies, please see Facebook's privacy policy.  
[Google Plus](http://plus.google.com/)| Sharing Plugin| We use a Google plugin to display the Google +1 button on our pages. This sets cookies, please see Google's privacy policy.  
[Twitter](http://www.twitter.com/)| Sharing Plugin| We use a Twitter plugin to display the Tweet button on our pages. This sets cookies, please see Twitter's privacy policy.  
[AddThis](http://www.addthis.com/privacy)| Sharing Plugin| We use a multi service plugin from AddThis to display sharing buttons. This sets cookies, please see their data collection policy.  
  
At First Class Watches we value our customer's privacy. When placing an order we encrypt all your details during transmission and only share identifiable and personal details when it is necessary to process your order (for example payment providers, courier companies). Your personal details are kept only in connection with your order. All credit and debit card numbers are encrypted using industry standard SSL security before it is sent to us, so it cannot be seen by any unauthorised party. Sometimes anonymous details of transactions are shared with third parties to allow us to measure performance of advertising and affiliated partners (for example cashback and voucher websites) to allow us to provide better service. Your personal information is not shared with these companies.

Information gathered from the use of cookies and our website is stored by ourselves is stored either by IP address in the form of access logs or in connection with your customer account. For non-personal information stored by third parties such as for Google Analytics you are advised to consult their privacy policies for information on data collection and retention. We use the information provided by this service to optimise the speed and content of our website, as well as for marketing purposes. It includes but is not limited to web browser (and version), operating system, screen resolution, country and region, time of visit, pages visited and referring website such as Google or advertising partners. No personal information (eg. names, full address or telephone numbers) is made available to Google Analytics.
